Jagdish Mehra Collection
University of Houston Libraries
- Oral Recording
  - C.D. 7.9.2 Item 2 - V. Weisskoff 1 of 2, June 7, 1988 (Box 123, Item 9)
  - C.D. 7.9.2 Item 2 - V. Weisskoff 2 of 2, June 7, 1988 (Box 123, Item 10)
  - C.D. 7.10.1 Item 1 - H.B.G. Casimir 1 of 2, March 16, 1991 (Box 123, Item 11)
  - C.D. 7.10.1 Item 1 - H.B.G. Casimir 2 of 2, March 16, 1991 (Box 123, Item 12)
  - C.D. 7.10.2 Item 2 - H.B.G. Casimir 1 of 2, March 16, 1991 (Box 123, Item 13)
  - C.D. 7.10.2 Item 2 - H.B.G. Casimir 2 of 2, March 16, 1991 (Box 123, Item 14)
  - C.D. 7.11.1 Item 1 - Al Hibbs 1 of 2, March 23, 1988 (Box 123, Item 15)
  - C.D. 7.11.1 Item 1 - Al Hibbs 2 of 2, March 23, 1988 (Box 123, Item 16)
  - C.D. 7.11.2 Item 2 - Al Hibbs 1 of 1, March 23, 1988 (Box 123, Item 17)
  - C.D. 7.12.1 Item 1 - Telegdi 1 of 2, January 19, 1988 (Box 123, Item 18)
  - C.D. 7.12.1 Item 1 - Telegdi 2 of 2, January 19, 1988 (Box 123, Item 19)
  - C.D. 7.13.1 Item 2 - Telegdi 1 of 2, January 19, 1988 (Box 123, Item 20)
  - C.D. 7.13.1 Item 2 - Telegdi 2 of 2, January 19, 1988 (Box 123, Item 21)
  - C.D. 7.13.1 Item 1 - Michael Cohen 1 of 2, March 24, 1989 (Box 123, Item 22)
  - C.D. 7.13.1 Item 1 - Michael Cohen 2 of 2, March 24, 1989 (Box 123, Item 23)
  - C.D. 7.13.2 Item 2 - Michael Cohen 1 of 1, March 24, 1989 (Box 123, Item 24)
  - C.D. 7.14.1 Item 1 - M. Sands 1 of 2, August 31, 1990 (Box 124, Item 1)
  - C.D. 7.14.1 Item 1 - M. Sands 2 of 2, August 31, 1990 (Box 124, Item 2)
  - C.D. 7.15.1 Item 1 - M. Meselson and R.S. Edgar 1 of 2, September 14-15, 1990 (Box 124, Item 3)
  - C.D. 7.15.1 Item 1 - M. Meselson and R.S. Edgar 2 of 2, September 14-15, 1990 (Box 124, Item 4)
  - C.D. 7.16.1 Item 1 - J. Wheeler 1 of 2, September 19, 1990 (Box 124, Item 5)
  - C.D. 7.16.1 Item 1 - J. Wheeler 2 of 2, September 19, 1990 (Box 124, Item 6)
  - C.D. 7.17.1 Item 1 - S. Berman 1 of 2 (Box 124, Item 7)
  - C.D. 7.17.1 Item 1 - S. Berman 2 of 2 (Box 124, Item 8)
  - C.D. 7.18.1 Item 1 - D. Amati 1 of 1, April 13, 1989 (Box 124, Item 9)
  - C.D. 7.19.1 Item 1 - F. Boehm and A. Sirlin 1 of 2, April 13, 1990 (Box 124, Item 10)
  - C.D. 7.19.1 Item 1 - F. Boehm and A. Sirlin 2 of 2, April 13, 1990 (Box 124, Item 11)
  - C.D. 7.20.1 Item 1 - Interview with Wightman 1 of 2, February 24, 1987 (Box 124, Item 12)
  - C.D. 7.20.1 Item 1 - Interview with Wightman 2 of 2, February 24, 1987 (Box 124, Item 13)
  - C.D. 7.21.1 Item 1 - Geoffrey Fox and Elmer Heller 1 of 1, November 23, 1988 (Box 124, Item 14)
  - C.D. 1.1.1 Item 1 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Margaret Mead, 1 of 1, February, 11, 1966 (Box 125, Item 1)
  - C.D. 1.1.2 Item 2 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Jerome Weisner, 1 of 2, October 28, 1966 (Box 125, Item 2)
  - C.D. 1.1.2 Item 2 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities SeriesL: Jerome Weisner, 2 of 2, October 28, 1966 (Box 125, Item 3)
  - C.D. 1.1.3 Item 3 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Archibald Macleish, 1 of 2, 1966 (Box 125, Item 4)
  - C.D. 1.1.3 Item 3 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Archibald Macleish, 2 of 2, 1966 (Box 125, Item 5)
  - C.D. 1.1.4 Item 4 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Willard Sloan Coffin, 1 of 2, March 10, 1967 (Box 125, Item 6)
  - C.D. 1.1.4 Item 4 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Willard Sloan Coffin, 2 of 2, March 10, 1967 (Box 125, Item 7)
  - C.D. 1.1.5 Item 5 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Handlin, 1 of 2, February 4, 1966 (Box 125, Item 8)
  - C.D. 1.1.5 Item 5 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Handlin, 2 of 2, February 4, 1966 (Box 125, Item 9)
  - C.D. 1.1.6 Item 6- Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Gerald Holton, 1 of 1, April 29, 1966 (Box 125, Item 10)
  - C.D. 1.1.7 Item 7 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Philip Morrison, 1 of 2, February 1966 (Box 125, Item 11)
  - C.D. 1.1.7 Item 7 - Southern Massachusetts Humanities Series: Philip Morrison, February 2 of 2, 1966 (Box 125, Item 12)
  - C.D. 1.2.1 Item 1 - Symposium of the Physicists Conception of Nature- Opening Session: The Astronomical Universe, D. Sciama, 1 of 4, September 18, 1972 (Box 125, Item 13)
  - C.D. 1.2.1 Item 1 - Symposium of the Physicists Conception of Nature- Opening Session: The Astronomical Universe, D. Sciama, 2 of 4, September 18, 1972 (Box 125, Item 14)
  - C.D. 1.2.1 Item 1 - Symposium of the Physicists Conception of Nature- Opening Session: The Astronomical Universe, D. Sciama, 3 of 4, September 18, 1972 (Box 125, Item 15)
  - C.D. 1.2.1 Item 1 - Symposium of the Physicists Conception of Nature- Opening Session: The Astronomical Universe, D. Sciama, 4 of 4, September 18, 1972 (Box 125, Item 16)
  - C.D. 1.2.2 Item 2 - Nature and Structure of Space-Time, J. Ehlers 1 of 4 (Box 125, Item 17)
  - C.D. 1.2.2 Item 2 - Nature and Structure of Space-Time, J. Ehlers 2 of 4 (Box 125, Item 18)
  - C.D. 1.2.2 Item 2 - Development of the Physicists Conception of Nature, P.A.M. Dirac 3 of 4 (Box 125, Item 19)
  - C.D. 1.2.2 Item 2 - Development of the Physicists Conception of Nature, P.A.M. Dirac 4 of 4 (Box 125, Item 20)
  - C.D. 1.2.3 Item 3 - Theory of Gravitation, A. Trautman 1 of 3 (Box 125, Item 21)
  - C.D. 1.2.3 Item 3 - The Role of General Relativity, J. Wheeler 2 of 3 (Box 125, Item 22)
  - C.D. 1.2.3 Item 3 - The Role of General Relativity, J. Wheeler 3 of 3 (Box 125, Item 23)
  - C.D. 1.2.4 Item 4 - Development and Problems of Quanta Theory, L. Rosenfeld and From Matrix Mechanics and Wave Mechanics to Unified Theory B.L. Van der Warden 1 of 4 (Box 125, Item 24)
  - C.D. 1.2.4 Item 4 - Development and Problems of Quanta Theory, L. Rosenfeld and From Matrix Mechanics and Wave Mechanics to Unified Theory B.L. Van der Warden 2 of 4 (Box 125, Item 25)
  - C.D. 1.2.4 Item 4 - Fundamental Aspects of the Symmetries of Nature, C. N. Yang 3 of 4 (Box 125, Item 26)
  - C.D. 1.2.4 Item 4 - Fundamental Aspects of the Symmetries of Nature, C. N. Yang 4 of 4 (Box 125, Item 27)
  - C.D. 1.2.5 Item 5 - Fundamental Constants and Their Development Time, P.A.M Dirac 1 of 3 (Box 125, Item 28)
  - C.D. 1.2.5 Item 5 - Fundamental Constants and Their Development Time, P.A.M Dirac 2 of 3 (Box 125, Item 29)
  - C.D. 1.2.5 Item 5 - Development and Conceptual Problems of Quantum Mechanics, W. Heisenberg 3 of 3 (Box 126, Item 1)
  - C.D. 1.2.6 Item 6 - Relative Equations in Quantum Mechanics, E. Wigner 1 of 3 (Box 126, Item 2)
  - C.D. 1.2.6 Item 6 - Relative Equations in Quantum Mechanics, E. Wigner 2 of 3 (Box 126, Item 3)
  - C.D. 1.2.6 Item 6 -The Classical Electron, F. Rohrlich 3 of 3 (Box 126, Item 4)
  - C.D. 1.2.7 Item 7 - Foundation and Development of Quantum Filed Theory, R. Peierls 1 of 3 (Box 126, Item 5)
  - C.D. 1.2.7 Item 7 - Superconductivity and Superfluidity and Discussion on Science and Military, H.B.G. Casimir 2 of 3 (Box 126, Item 6)
  - C.D. 1.2.7 Item 7 - Superconductivity and Superfluidity and Discussion on Science and Military, H.B.G. Casimir 3 of 3 (Box 126, Item 7)
  - C.D. 1.2.8 Item 8 - Mathematical Structure of Quantum Theory, J.M. Jauch 1 of 2 (Box 126, Item 8)
  - C.D. 1.2.8 Item 8 - Development of Quantum Electrodynamics, J. Schwinger 2 of 2 (Box 126, Item 9)
  - C.D. 1.2.9 Item 9 - Progress in Renormalization Theory, Abdus Salam 1 of 4 (Box 126, Item 10)
  - C.D. 1.2.9 Item 9 - Progress in Renormalization Theory, Abdus Salam 2 of 4 (Box 126, Item 11)
  - C.D. 1.2.9 Item 9 - Crucial Experimental in Quantum Phenomenon, V. Telegdi 3 of 4 (Box 126, Item 12)
  - C.D. 1.2.9 Item 9 - Crucial Experimental in Quantum Phenomenon,V. Telegdi 4 of 4 (Box 126, Item 13)
  - C.D. 1.2.10 Item 10 - Reception and Banquet in Honour of P.A.M. Dirac 1 of 1 (Box 126, Item 14)
  - C.D. 1.2.11 Item 11 - W. Thirring, W. Pauli's Scientific Work, C.P. Enz 1 of 3 (Box 126, Item 15)
  - C.D. 1.2.11 Item 11 - W. Thirring, W. Pauli's Scientific Work, C.P. Enz 2 of 3 (Box 126, Item 16)
  - C.D. 1.2.11 Item 11 - Crucial Experiments in Quantum Phenomena, W. Lamb 3 of 3 (Box 126, Item 17)
  - C.D. 1.2.12 Item 12 - Problems of Statistical Physics, G Uhlenbeck and Microscopic and Macroscopic Description of Equilibrium, M. Kac 1 of 4 (Box 126, Item 18)
  - C.D. 1.2.12 Item 12 - Kinetic Approach to Non-Equilibrium Phenomenon, E.G.D. Cohen and Dynamics, Probability, and Entropy, I. Prigogine 3 of 4 (Box 126, Item 19)
  - C.D. 1.2.12 Item 12 - Kinetic Approach to Non-Equilibrium Phenomenon, E.G.D. Cohen and Dynamics, Probability, and Entropy, I. Prigogine 4 of 4 (Box 126, Item 20)
  - C.D. 1.2.13 Item 13 - Biological Structure, M. Eigen 1 of 4 (Box 126, Item 21)
  - C.D. 1.2.13 Item 13 - Biological Structure, M. Eigen 2 of 4 (Box 126, Item 22)
  - C.D. 1.2.13 Item 13 - The Expanding Earth, P. Jordan 3 of 4 (Box 126, Item 23)
  - C.D. 1.2.13 Item 13 - The Expanding Earth, P. Jordan 4 of 4 (Box 126, Item 24)
  - C.D. 1.2.14 Item 14 - Classification and Quantum Descriptions, C.F. Von Weizsacker and Measurement Theory, Bell, D'Espagnat, Ludwig, Prigogine, Cooper, Jauch, Wigner 1 of 4 (Box 126, Item 25)
  - C.D. 1.2.14 Item 14 - Classification and Quantum Descriptions, C.F. Von Weizsacker and Measurement Theory, Bell, D'Espagnat, Ludwig, Prigogine, Cooper, Jauch, Wigner 2 of 4 (Box 126, Item 26)
  - C.D. 1.2.14 Item 14 - Objectivity and Measurement in Quantum Mechanics, R. Haag 3 of 4 (Box 126, Item 27)
  - C.D. 1.2.14 Item 14 - Objectivity and Measurement in Quantum Mechanics, R. Haag 4 of 4 (Box 126, Item 28)
  - C.D. 1.2.15 Item 15 - E. Fermi, S. Chandrasekhar BBC, P.A.M. Dirac 1 of 3 (Box 127, Item 1)
  - C.D. 1.2.15 Item 15 - Physics E Philosophy, Von Weizsacker 2 of 3 (Box 127, Item 2)
  - C.D. 1.2.15 Item 15 - Physics E Philosophy, Von Weizsacker 3 of 3 (Box 127, Item 3)
  - C.D. 1.3.1 Item 1 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, P.A.M. Dirac 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 4)
  - C.D. 1.3.2 Item 2 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Heisenberg 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 5)
  - C.D. 1.3.3 Item 3 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Wigner 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 6)
  - C.D. 1.3.4 Item 4 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Bethe 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 7)
  - C.D. 1.3.5 Item 5 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, The Language and Life, Dr. George Beadle 1 of 1, February 5, 1970 (Box 127, Item 8)
  - C.D. 1.3.6 Item 6 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, C.P. Snow, April 12, 1970 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 9)
  - C.D. 1.3.7 Item 7 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Dirac on Gravitation 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 10)
  - C.D. 1.3.8 Item 8 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Lecture at J.M.'s Invitation, Tape I - P.A.M. Dirac 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 11)
  - C.D. 1.3.9 Item 9 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Lecture at J.M.'s Invitation, Tape II - P.A.M. Dirac 1 of 1 (Box 127, Item 12)
  - C.D. 1.3.10 Item 10 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Alexander Hollander 1 of 1, May 4, 1970 (Box 127, Item 13)
  - C.D. 1.3.11 Item 11 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Dr. Seshachar 1 of 2, October 19, 1970 (Box 127, Item 14)
  - C.D. 1.3.11 Item 11 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Dr. Seshachar 2 of 2, October 19, 1970 (Box 127, Item 15)
  - C.D. 1.3.12 Item 12 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Mendelson 1 of 2, May 27, 1970 (Box 127, Item 16)
  - C.D. 1.3.12 Item 12 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Mendelson 2 of 2, May 27, 1970 (Box 127, Item 17)
  - C.D. 1.3.13 Item 13 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Robert Marshak 1 of 2, April 7, 1970 (Box 127, Item 18)
  - C.D. 1.3.13 Item 13 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Robert Marshak 2 of 2, April 7, 1970 (Box 127, Item 19)
  - C.D. 1.3.14 Item 14 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Abdus Salam 1 of 2, April 17, 1970 (Box 127, Item 20)
  - C.D. 1.3.14 Item 14 - Public Understanding of Science Series - The University of Texas at Austin, Abdus Salam 2 of 2, April 17, 1970 (Box 127, Item 21)
  - C.D. 2.1.1 Item 1 - Feynman-Mehra Converse - Past Decade in Particle Theory, The University of Texas at Austin 1 of 4, April 18, 1970 (Box 127, Item 22)
  - C.D. 2.1.1 Item 1 - Feynman-Mehra Converse - Past Decade in Particle Theory, The University of Texas at Austin 2 of 4, April 18, 1970 (Box 127, Item 23)
  - C.D. 2.1.1 Item 1 - Feynman-Mehra Converse - Past Decade in Particle Theory, The University of Texas at Austin 3 of 4, April 18, 1970 (Box 127, Item 24)
  - C.D. 2.1.1 Item 1 - Feynman-Mehra Converse - Past Decade in Particle Theory, The University of Texas at Austin 4 of 4, April 18, 1970 (Box 127, Item 25)
  - C.D. 2.2.1 Item 1 - Freeman Dyson Interviewed by Mehra 1 of 2, January 1970 (Box 127, Item 26)
  - C.D. 2.2.1 Item 1 - Freeman Dyson Interviewed by Mehra 2 of 2, January 1970 (Box 127, Item 27)
  - C.D. 2.2.2 Item 2 - Freeman Dyson Interviewed by Mehra 1 of 4, January 1970 (Box 128, Item 1)
  - C.D. 2.2.2 Item 2 - Freeman Dyson Interviewed by Mehra 2 of 4, January 1970 (Box 128, Item 2)
  - C.D. 2.2.2 Item 2 - Freeman Dyson Interviewed by Mehra 3 of 4, January 1970 (Box 128, Item 3)
  - C.D. 2.2.2 Item 2 - Freeman Dyson Interviewed by Mehra 4 of 4, January 1970 (Box 128, Item 4)
  - C.D. 2.3.1 Item 1 - Conversation about Bose's Scientific Work and Association with Einstein 1 of 2, August 30, 1970 (Box 128, Item 5)
  - C.D. 2.3.1 Item 1 - Conversation about Bose's Scientific Work and Association with Einstein 2 of 2, August 30, 1970 (Box 128, Item 6)
  - C.D. 2.3.2 Item 2 - Conversation about Bose's Scientific Work and Association with Einstein 1 of 2, August 30, 1970 (Box 128, Item 7)
  - C.D. 2.3.2 Item 2 - Conversation about Bose's Scientific Work and Association with Einstein 2 of 2, August 30, 1970 (Box 128, Item 8)
  - C.D. 2.4.1 Item 1 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 1 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 9)
  - C.D. 2.4.1 Item 1 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 2 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 10)
  - C.D. 2.4.1 Item 1 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 3 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 11)
  - C.D. 2.4.1 Item 1 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 4 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 12)
  - C.D. 2.4.2 Item 2 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 1 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 13)
  - C.D. 2.4.2 Item 2 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 2 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 14)
  - C.D. 2.4.2 Item 2 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 3 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 15)
  - C.D. 2.4.2 Item 2 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Leon Rosenfeld, Development of Atomic Physics 4 of 4, April 20, 1970 (Box 128, Item 16)
  - C.D. 2.4.3 Item 3 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century, Leon Rosenfeld 1 of 5 (Box 128, Item 17)
  - C.D. 2.4.3 Item 3 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 2 of 5 (Box 128, Item 18)
  - C.D. 2.4.3 Item 3 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 3 of 5 (Box 128, Item 19)
  - C.D. 2.4.3 Item 3 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 4 of 5 (Box 128, Item 20)
  - C.D. 2.4.3 Item 3 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 5 of 5 (Box 128, Item 21)
  - C.D. 2.4.4 Item 4 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 1 of 4 (Box 128, Item 22)
  - C.D. 2.4.4 Item 4 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 2 of 4 (Box 128, Item 23)
  - C.D. 2.4.4 Item 4 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 3 of 4 (Box 128, Item 24)
  - C.D. 2.4.4 Item 4 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 4 of 4 (Box 128, Item 25)
  - C.D. 2.4.5 Item 5 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 1 of 4 (Box 129, Item 1)
  - C.D. 2.4.5 Item 5 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 2 of 4 (Box 129, Item 2)
  - C.D. 2.4.5 Item 5 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 3 of 4 (Box 129, Item 3)
  - C.D. 2.4.5 Item 5 - Development of Atomic Physics - Development of Physics in the 20th Century,Leon Rosenfeld 4 of 4 (Box 129, Item 4)
  - C.D. 2.5.1 Item 1 - Mehra Conversation with Heisenberg, Munich 1 of 1, May 22, 1969 (Box 129, Item 5)
  - C.D. 2.6.1 Item 1 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Dirac, Center for Theoretical Studies in Miami 1 of 2, March 28, 1969 (Box 129, Item 6)
  - C.D. 2.6.1 Item 1 - Dr. Mehra Conversation with Dirac, Center for Theoretical Studies in Miami 2 of 2, March 28, 1969 (Box 129, Item 7)
  - C.D. 2.7.1 Item 1 - Eugene Walker Lectures at The University of Texas, Austin, Invited by Dr. Mehra, 1 of 2, November 18, 1969 (Box 129, Item 8)
  - C.D. 2.7.1 Item 1 - Eugene Walker Lectures at The University of Texas, Austin, Invited by Dr. Mehra 2 of 2, November 18, 1969 (Box 129, Item 9)
  - C.D. 2.8.1 Item 1 - Discussion with Eugene Walker, Princeton 1 of 3, May 13-14, 1970 (Box 129, Item 10)
  - C.D. 2.8.1 Item 1 - Discussion with Eugene Walker, Princeton 2 of 3, May 13-14, 1970 (Box 129, Item 11)
  - C.D. 2.8.1 Item 1 - Discussion with Eugene Walker, Princeton 3 of 3, May 13-14, 1970 (Box 129, Item 12)
  - C.D. 2.9.1 Item 1 - Sudarshan and Mehra, University of Syracuse, December 23, 1966 and February 1, 1967 1 of 5 (Box 129, Item 13)
  - C.D. 2.9.1 Item 1 - Sudarshan and Mehra, University of Syracuse, December 23, 1966 and February 1, 1967 2 of 5 (Box 129, Item 14)
  - C.D. 2.9.1 Item 1 - Sudarshan and Mehra, University of Syracuse, December 23, 1966 and February 1, 1967 3 of 5 (Box 129, Item 15)
  - C.D. 2.9.1 Item 1 - Sudarshan and Mehra, University of Syracuse, December 23, 1966 and February 1, 1967 4 of 5 (Box 129, Item 16)
  - C.D. 2.9.1 Item 1 - Sudarshan and Mehra, University of Syracuse, December 23, 1966 and February 1, 1967 5 of 5 (Box 129, Item 17)
  - C.D. 2.10.1 Item 1 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 1 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 18)
  - C.D. 2.10.1 Item 1 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 2 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 19)
  - C.D. 2.10.1 Item 1 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 3 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 20)
  - C.D. 2.10.1 Item 1 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 3 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 21)
  - C.D. 2.10.1 Item 1 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 4 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 22)
  - C.D. 2.10.2 Item 2 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 1 of 1, 1968 (Box 129, Item 23)
  - C.D. 2.10.3 Item 3 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 1 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 24)
  - C.D. 2.10.3 Item 3 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 2 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 25)
  - C.D. 2.10.3 Item 3 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 3 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 26)
  - C.D. 2.10.3 Item 3 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 3 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 27)
  - C.D. 2.10.3 Item 3 - Trieste Symposium: Conversations with Klein, Wigner, Dirac, Salam, Lifschitz, Bethe, and Heisenberg 4 of 4, 1968 (Box 129, Item 28)
  - C.D. 2.11.1 Item 1 - Mehra Conversations with Wigner and Sudarshan, The University of Texas, Austin: Fundamental Problems of Modern Physics 1 of 5, November 25, 1969 (Box 130, Item 1)
  - C.D. 2.11.1 Item 1 - Mehra Conversations with Wigner and Sudarshan, The University of Texas, Austin: Fundamental Problems of Modern Physics 2 of 5, November 25, 1969 (Box 130, Item 2)
  - C.D. 2.11.1 Item 1 - Mehra Conversations with Wigner and Sudarshan, The University of Texas, Austin: Fundamental Problems of Modern Physics 3 of 5, November 25, 1969 (Box 130, Item 3)
  - C.D. 2.11.1 Item 1 - Mehra Conversations with Wigner and Sudarshan, The University of Texas, Austin: Fundamental Problems of Modern Physics 4 of 5, November 25, 1969 (Box 130, Item 4)
  - C.D. 2.11.1 Item 1 - Mehra Conversations with Wigner and Sudarshan, The University of Texas, Austin: Fundamental Problems of Modern Physics 5 of 5, November 25, 1969 (Box 130, Item 5)
  - C.D. 3.1.1 Item 1 - Conversation with Eugene Wigner 1 of 2, February 24, 1987 (Box 130, Item 6)
  - C.D. 3.1.1 Item 1 - Conversation with Eugene Wigner 2 of 2 (Box 130, Item 7)
  - C.D. 3.2.1 Item 2 - Conversation with Eugene Wigner 1 of 2 (Box 130, Item 8)
  - C.D. 3.2.1 Item 2 - Conversation with Eugene Wigner 2 of 2 (Box 130, Item 9)
  - C.D. 3.1.3 Item 3 - Conversation with Eugene Wigner 1 of 1 (Box 130, Item 10)
  - C.D. 3.2.1 Item 1 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 11)
  - C.D. 3.2.1 Item 1 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 2 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 12)
  - C.D. 3.2.2 Item 2 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 13)
  - C.D. 3.2.2 Item 2 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 2 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 14)
  - C.D. 3.2.3 Item 3 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 15)
  - C.D. 3.2.3 Item 3 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 2 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 16)
  - C.D. 3.2.4 Item 4 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 1, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 17)
  - C.D. 3.2.5 Item 5 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 1, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 18)
  - C. D. 3.2.6 Item 6 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 19)
  - C. D. 3.2.6 Item 6 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 2 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 20)
  - C.D. 3.2.7 Item 7 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 21)
  - C.D. 3.2.7 Item 7 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 2 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 22)
  - C.D. 3.2.8 Item 8 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 23)
  - C.D. 3.2.8 Item 8 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 2 of 2, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 24)
  - C.D. 3.2.9 Item 9 - Conversation with Richard Feynman 1 of 1, January 1980 (Box 130, Item 25)
  - C.D. 3.3.1 Item 1 - Conversation with Feynman Dyson 1 of 2, February 25, 1987 (Box 130, Item 26)
  - C.D. 3.3.1 Item 1 - Conversation with Feynman Dyson 2 of 2, February 25, 1987 (Box 130, Item 27)
  - C.D. 3.3.2 Item 2 - Conversation with Feynman Dyson 1 of 2, February 25, 1987 (Box 130, Item 28)
  - C.D. 3.3.2 Item 2 -Conversation with Feynman Dyson 2 of 2, February 25, 1987 (Box 130, Item 29)
  - C.D. 3.3.3 Item 3 - Conversation with Feynman Dyson 1 of 2, February 25, 1987 (Box 131, Item 1)